Kettle and the Oideru~.
The third is comedy.
And now, the third one. Comedy.
Yes. Comedy. I like comedy,
This is the one to watch.
Yes. The one who watches.
The one who watches. I like to watch, not to perform.
What kind of comedy do you like to watch?
I like to watch comedy comedy acts, manzai, and stories,
I also like variety shows.
Is there any particular group that you particularly enjoy watching now?
There are many comedians I like,
Longcoat Darling.
Long Coat Darling?
Yes.
What about Longcoat Darling?
I like his comedy and his stories.
What do you mean?
Is it something to do with the voice?
It's like a fantasy or something,
It's the sense of language that sticks with me.
It sticks.
The one that sticks is Mr. Longcoat Darling.
And the peaceful feeling.
Peaceful?
A sense of not hurting.
I see.
It's not about dropping your hair.
The worldview was very loose and relaxed,
That really stuck with me.
Do you go to comedy gigs?
I don't have a theater in Tohoku, so I don't get to go very often,
I went to one in Tokyo the other day.
I see.
That must have been a pretty casual time for you, wasn't it?
It was very interesting.
That's what I like about comedy,
No matter how much pain you are going through,
I always felt energized when I saw a comedy.
That's how I was always cheered up,
That's what I really like about comedy.
But you are quite active, aren't you?
I see.
I'm just talking about the active part,
I actually stay at home all the time.
But I do have the energy to do what I want to do and say what I want to say,
I am very active in what I want to do, what I want to say, and so on.
Good.
And maybe some live comedy?
Do you listen to the radio?
I listen to the radio.
Really? You like it?
I joined a paid radio station,
I joined a paid radio club, and I can't listen to the radio in some areas.
What is a paid radio station?
Radio pay-per-view?
Radio Co Premier nationwide.
Yes, that's right.
Can I listen to it?
Yes, I can listen to it.
I have a subscription.
For example, I can listen to broadcasts from Fukuoka.
And even if you can't listen to it in real time, you can listen to it later.
Yes, yes.
I can also listen to late-night programs.
It's a convenient world we live in now.
So you can check the room.
I understand.
The third element is comedy.
I finally learned something.
It was interesting.
Courtesy of Runchan Sukiskikomio.
Thank you very much.
Seino
Happy rune